{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How many wheels are F1 cars have?",
      "options": ["6", "4", "2", "8"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which constructor has the most victory in the history of F1? ",
      "options": ["Renualt", "Mercedes", "Red Bull", "Ferrari"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many points does champoin recieve in a grand prix?",
      "options": ["25", "18", "10", "8"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the greatest driver in F1 history?",
      "options": [
        "Micheal Schumacher",
        "Max Verstapean",
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Sebastian Vettel"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the common driver champion?",
      "options": [
        "Max Verstapean",
        "Charles Lecrec",
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Goerge Russel"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How F1 Motors cars are working?",
      "options": ["Electronic", "Hybrid", "Feul", "Sun"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When drivers can use DRS?",
      "options": [
        "Whenever they want",
        "Whenever they are in the straight path",
        "Whenever they break",
        "Whenever they want to pass another and they have permission"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which circuit is the fastest in F1 history?",
      "options": ["Azerbaijan", "Spa", "Jaddeh", "Austin"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which circuit is the most danagerous circiut in F1 history?",
      "options": ["Imola", "Monaco, Monte Carlo", "Spa", "Nurbergring"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which driver has won the most time Monaco grand prix?",
      "options": [
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Micheal Schumacher",
        "Niki Lauda",
        "Ayrton Senna"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When FIA gives a red flag in a race?",
      "options": [
        "In every race",
        "Whenever a normal accident is happens.",
        "Whenever a high risk accident is happens",
        "Whenever race starts"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When Hybrind era began?",
      "options": ["1950", "2014", "2026", "1975"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many types of tires F1 has and which one is faster?",
      "options": ["4, hard", "2, full wet", "4, soft", "1, medium"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which circuit is the oldest in F1 history?",
      "options": ["Monaco", "Spa", "Silverstone", "Zandvoort"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "How many Silenders F1 cars have?",
      "options": ["8", "12", "4", "6"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
